Finding Aid for Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers
Clarke Historical Library
- Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers.
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,November 17, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,November 22, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,December 1, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,December 1, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,December 3, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,December 6, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,December 9, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,December 15, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,December 13, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,January 3, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,January 6, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,January 19, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,January 20, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,January 27, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,January 29, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Santa Claus,December 24, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - Correspondence to: Mother From: ND (folder 1 of 2),1894 (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - Correspondence to: Mother From: ND (folder 2 of 2),1894 (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - Correspondence to: Mother From: ND,February 15, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - Correspondence to: Aunt and Uncle From: Anna,March 26, 1897 (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,March 31, 1897 (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - Correspondence to: Mother From: ND,March 18, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mother,April 1, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: Nellie,undated (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - Correspondence to: (Davis) Children From: Father (W. H. Davis),August 25, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,January 26, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - Correspondence to: Little Sister (ND?) From: Zora,September 25, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Uncle Weston Davis,February 13, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 290)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Aunt Loretta Davis,February 13, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - Correspondence to: Little Girl (ND?) From: Mama,undated (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Uncle Weston Davis,June 18, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - Correspondence to: Daughter (ND?) From: Parents,October 25, [no year] (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,October 29, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. Allen From: ND,undated (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,November 22, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,January 1, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 298)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Father,January 9, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mother,February 13, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,March 19, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 301)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,April 30, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,May 23, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,July 5, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,July 6, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,July 7, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - Correspondence to: ND and All From: Parents,July 10, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,July 12, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Father,August 2, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,September 29, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mother,September 30, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,October 4, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,October 7, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 313)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,October 10, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents, with First Art Recital,October 11, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,October 14, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,October 17, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,October 24, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,October 26, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Marna,October 31, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,November 4, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 321)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,November 7, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,November 11, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 323)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,November 11, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,November 19, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 325)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,undated (Box 4, Folder 326)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,December 3, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,December 6, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,December 12, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,December 17, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,January 3, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,January 13, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 332)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,January 16, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 333)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mr. Ludlow,January 16, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 334)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,February 3, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 335)
  - Correspondence to: Daughter (ND?) From: Father,February 5, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 336)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,February 5, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 337)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,February 7, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 338)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,February 10, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 339)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,February 17, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 340)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,February 18, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 341)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,February 28, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 342)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,March 1, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 343)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,March 10, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 344)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,April 2, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 345)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,April 11, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 346)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,April 14, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 347)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,April 20, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 348)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,April 23, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 349)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,April 27, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 350)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,April 29, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 351)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,May 5, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 352)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,May 19, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 353)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,May 26, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 354)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mama (folder 1 of 2),undated (Box 4, Folder 355)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mama (folder 2 of 2),undated (Box 4, Folder 356)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,May 28, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 357)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mother (folder 1 of 2),undated (Box 4, Folder 357)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mother (folder 2 of 2), undated; with Michigan State Normal College Commencement Week Material, June 16-19, 1907June 16-19, 1907, undated (Box 4, Folder 358)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,June 9, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 359)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,September 30, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 360)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,undated (Box 4, Folder 361)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,October 3, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 362)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,October 10, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 363)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,October 11, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 364)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,October 17, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 365)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,undated (Box 4, Folder 366)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,October 20, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 367)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,October 27, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 368)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mother,October 30, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 369)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,undated (Box 4, Folder 370)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,November 3, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 371)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,November 7, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 372)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,November 10, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 373)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,undated (Box 4, Folder 374)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,November 12, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 375)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,November 17, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 376)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,December 4, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 377)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,December 9, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 378)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,December 11, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 379)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,December 15, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 380)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,December 17, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 381)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,undated (Box 4, Folder 382)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,January 5, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 383)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,January 9, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 384)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,January 14, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 385)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,January 19, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 386)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,January 26, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 387)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,January 28, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 388)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,February 2, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 389)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,February 9, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 390)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,February 11, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 391)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Mama,February 12, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 392)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,February 16, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 393)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,February 17, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 394)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: ND,February 23, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 395)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,February 25, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 396)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,February 26, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 397)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,March 4, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 398)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,March 15, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 399)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,March 17, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 400)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Parents,March 24, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 401)
  - NDF, Miscellaneous Thank You Notes, Croquet Rules,May 7, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - ND, Diary,1902 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Theron W. Finley, School Reports,November 27, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Harry C. Finley, School Reports,1921, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: Vera VanSchelen,December 21, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,February 20, [no year] (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Parma Chapter Order of the Eastern Star (O.E.S.) ,1912-1913 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence to: Friend From: Franklyn Manufacturing Company,July [no day], 1925 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - W. H. Davis, Tax Receipt,December 21, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - W. H. Davis, Certificate for Justice of the Peace,August 29, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: University of Michigan Archives,November 17, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Michigan Historical Commission, Theron S. Finley / ND Wedding Clipping and Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings,May 5, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to: Whom It May Concern From: Theron W. and Harry C. Finley,July 30, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence to: Mary MacMurtrie From: R. B. Hampton,June 18, 18[no date] (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - W. H. Davis, Second Grade Teachers' Certificates,1867, 1870, 1880, 1882 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: J. W. Bentley; Michigan Teachers Reading Circle; Michigan State Teachers Association Institute Program,September 11, 1882; 1916/1917; November 1916 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Jackson High School, Teachers' Meeting,October 1916 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Common Schools of Michigan, Spring Term Examination,1910 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Albion Council of the Michigan Congress of Parents and Teachers,February 12, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Miss R. Landon,October 30, [no year] (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Chauncey Deming Searl, Obituary Card and Photograph,August 31, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. [no "s"] Nellie D. Finley From: Michigan Mutual Hail Insurance Company,June 27, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Moore, Genealogy,1886 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: M. J.,February 28, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - W. H. Davis, Lakeview, Michigan Lot, Miscellaneous Receipts,1888-1890 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - ND, Cato Township, Montcalm County, Tax Receipt,1891 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - W. H. Davis, Lodge Dues Receipt,1891 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - W. H. Davis, St. Jo House Stationary, with Mecosta, Michigan, Thanksgiving Party Program,undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - ND, Women's Relief Corps Card,January 26, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - W. H. Davis, W. J. Carse; Quakerton Teachers; Graduation Class Speech,August 24, 1892; 1865-1918; 1900, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harry Brown, Michigan Historical Collections,March 11, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - ND, Lakeview Village Tax Receipt,August 15, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - NDF, Springport Signal,September 8, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - NDF, Albion Evening Reporter,September 12, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - NDF, Miscellaneous Recipe,March 3, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie,October 12, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence to: Louie Thompson From: Brenda,August 13, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. B. Genze,September 24, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty,January 29, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 12, [no year] (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,September 16, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Gerty and Wilson Davis,1933 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louis,February 2, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ruth Saxton,January 6, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis,December 27, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louis,February 21, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zarita,June 20, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe and Harry Davis,July 30, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie,August 24, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie,October 16, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,May 26, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. W. H. Davis From: Harry E. Davis,June 8, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - NDF, Springport Signal,June 3, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis, May 29, 1933; with Frank Hewitt / Lena Herrick Wedding Invitation, December 11, 1920,May 28, 1933; December 11, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - NDF and Family, Sympathy Letter / Flower List,August 11, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - H. J. McMurtrie Business Card,undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Farmers' Mutual Insurance Company of Jackson, Michigan, Financial Statement,undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Wilson and Gerty Davis,undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: E. E. Stokoe,1930s (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: State Farm Insurance Company,1932/1933 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Utica Public Schools,May 25, 1908 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - NDF, Guardianship Papers,1928 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - NDF, Bank Book,1944 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - NDF, American Magazine Advertisement, November 1931; Sentous High School Graduation Invitation, 1932; undated Photographs, Tintype Carte-de-visites, Theron and Nellie Photograph Christmas Postcard; George T. Bullen and Company, Albion, Michigan, Sales Slip,November 1931; 1932; undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and Family From: Various Friends, Postcards,1913-1949 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence to: Pa From: ND, 1894; Theron Finley Newspaper Clippings, undated,1894, undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W.H. Davis From: Mrs. J.A. Cornell,November 23, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Miscellaneous Notes, 1881-1882; Finley / Davis Wedding Newspaper Articles, undated; Peter C. Malaney, Michigan Mutual Life Insurance Business Card, Pocket Songster - Songs, Stories, Some in German; Wilson Case Newspaper Article (Reprint, 1927),1881-1882; 1927; undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: George H. Burr and Company,October 1932 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grand Rapids Trust Company,September 1933 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jackson County Examination Reports of Various Students, 1931; Wedding Announcement - Prine / Howard, 1927,1927; 1931 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: D. A. Waterman, May 28, 1908, 1908; Advertising Card (Fish) Black Cross Coffee, undated; Michigan State Normal College, Ypsilanti Commencement, 1907,1907-1908; undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Pruda,December 31, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Devereaux Hall Association Stock Certificate,1921 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - NDF, Car Registration,1932 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence to NDF? From: Jackson County Teachers', Circular Letter, September 1916; Business and Calling Cards, undated,September 1916; undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence to NDF From: N. A. Corbett, Telegram,November 19, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence to NDF From: Caroline Elmer, Student, October 3, 1928; with Michigan Souvenir booklet, 1897; Ladies' Notebook and Calendar, with Family Birth dates, undated; Hartford, Connecticut Weekly Times (newspaper), June 1, 1861,1861; 1897; 1928; undated (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - W. H. Davis, Insurance Policies, 1875-1937; Miscellaneous, 1975; Recipe book, circa 1865-1867; Recipes and Dr. Miles' Cookbook, undated,1865-1867, 1875-1937; 1975; undated (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jackson County Republican Committee 1936, with Michigan State College 69th Commencement Program, 1927,1927; 1936 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - NDF, Springport Chapter Order of the Eastern Star Certificate,1937 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Michigan State Normal College, Ypsilanti,1939 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: National Surety Company,1933 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: National Geographic Society,December 10, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - W. H. Davis, Knights of the Maccabees Certificate,1890 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - W. H. Davis, Jackson Life Underwriters' Association April 5, 1933; with Various Teachers' Term Reports, Springport and/or Parma, 1870s-1890s,1870s-1890s; 1933 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Martha J. Davis, Ladies of the Maccabees Certificate, 1899; Laws of, 1898; State of Michigan Assessor of School District Check Stub Book, 1889-1896; Hartford, Connecticut, Daily Times, June 24, 1861, Hartford, Connecticut,Weekly Times, August 6, 10, 24, 1861; Harpers Weekly (reissue), May 18, 1861; The Call (San Francisco), September 26, 1881; New York Herald (2 copies), April 15, 1865; Inquirer and Mirror (Nantucket, Massachusetts), October 7, 1960; Michigan Normal College blank stationary, undated; Michigan State Normal College Commencement Program, 1908,1861; 1864-1865; 1881; 1889-1896; 1908; 1960; undated (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Lyle A. Torrant, Commissioner of Schools, Jackson, February 5, 1947; with Parma Teachers' Contract, 1896; Parma and Springport Schools Classification Report, 1895; Michigan State Normal College Ivy Day Booklet, 1909; Michigan State Normal College Diploma, 1908; Annual Statistical Reports, Parma Schools, 1876-1903; Jackson County Teacher's Certificate, 1874; Teachers' Term Reports, the District Director, Parma, 1902-1905,1874; 1876-1905; 1908-1909; 1947 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Harry C. Finley, Michigan College of Mining and Technology, Report Card,1940 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - NDF?, Notebook About Classes and Accounts,1898-1901 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - NDF, Notebook About Trip to Niagara Falls, Canada, undated; Miscellaneous, undated; Holiday Greeting Cards, various dates,undated (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Bessie,January 1911 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Edna,January 2, November 1911 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Lena,January 6, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Hazel,January 9, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Uncle Weston Davis,January 15, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Herb Tweedie,January 16, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Harriet D.,January 19, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Sybil,January 29, 1911 (Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Floy,February 5, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Aunt Philena, with John Stamp's Obituary,February 7, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Edna,February 8, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtie From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,February 12, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Thomas Sattler,February 22, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Hattie,February 22, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Eva L. King, with Eastern Star Receipt,March 2, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Ida,March 2, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Orpha,March 4, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Uncle Weston Davis,March 5, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Anna Holland,March 6, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Bessie,March 6, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence to: ND (Children of all you address) From: Grandma, Hannah Moore, Lannie,March 7, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: A. T. Tweedie, with Instructions,March 15, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence to: John E. Kribble From: Mrs. Frank Krenerick,March 19, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley and Harmond Ruff From: Frank Krenerick,March 19, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Edna,March 22, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence to: ND, Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,March 23, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Marguerite Furey?,March 28, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Sybil,April 2, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence to: ND From: Aunt Philena, includes fabric and newspaper clipping,April 2, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 29)